{"test_questions": [[{"question": "The HIV virus infects primarily", "opta": "brain cells", "optb": "cells in the immune system", "optc": "red blood cells", "optd": "liver cells", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Chronic granulomatous disease results from a failure to perform oxidative burst. This deficiency would be most likely to interfere with", "opta": "CTL killing of viruses", "optb": "dendritic cell activation to become a mature APC", "optc": "infected cell processing of virus peptides", "optd": "macrophage intracellular killing of bacteria", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Difficulties with somatic gene therapy arise from all of the following except", "opta": "GVHD caused by mature T cells in the transplanted cells", "optb": "inserting a gene so that it will function properly", "optc": "limited life span of more mature hematopoietic cells", "optd": "transducing genetic material into stem cells", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A monoclonal antibody (mAb) specific for the 2,4-dinitrophenyl (DNP) hapten might also bind", "opta": "Leu or Ileu", "optb": "His or Pro", "optc": "Tyr or Phe", "optd": "Ser or Thr", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Retinoblastoma is due to a mutation in a", "opta": "kinase", "optb": "tumor supressor", "optc": "cyclin", "optd": "viral gene", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "An autoimmune disease is", "opta": "AIDS", "optb": "Measles", "optc": "Lupus", "optd": "Mumps", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "If Class IIMHC is not expressed in the thymus, the resulting immune deficiencies would include all of the following except reduced", "opta": "alternative complement activation.", "optb": "CD8 T cell-mediated cytotoxicity", "optc": "macrophage activation to vesicular pathogens", "optd": "IgG synthesis", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Specific translocations are associated with", "opta": "colon cancer", "optb": "breast cancer", "optc": "pancreatic cancer", "optd": "some leukemias", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "To treat HIV infections using drugs, the major problem is that", "opta": "the drugs that are good inhibitors cannot by synthesized", "optb": "the drugs interfere with normal digestion", "optc": "the virus particles with altered (mutant) proteases arise", "optd": "the drugs are rapidly degraded", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The primary reason for AIDS, a deadly disease is that it", "opta": "is caused by a virus", "optb": "is caused by a bacterium", "optc": "destroys key components of the body's internal defense system", "optd": "causes a breakdown of the body's inflammatory response", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A selective IgA deficiency would be expected to result in problems with", "opta": "bacterial infections", "optb": "infections following dental work due to bacteria entering the bloodstream", "optc": "mucosal pathogens", "optd": "pathogens which can survive inside macrophages", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Combined cellular and humoral immune deficiencies result from lack of all of the following except", "opta": "a thymus", "optb": "class II MHC", "optc": "HIV infection of CD4+ T cells", "optd": "transporter of antigen peptides (TAP)", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "An example of an immunodeficiency disorder is", "opta": "thyroiditis", "optb": "rheumatic fever", "optc": "systemic lupus erythematosus", "optd": "AIDS", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Bone marrow given to an infant with SCID must", "opta": "be irradiated to eliminate GVHD", "optb": "contain mature T cells that can begin making immune responses immediately", "optc": "come from a donor that shares some MHC alleles with the recipient", "optd": "come from one of the child's parents", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "X-linked hyper IgM syndrome, resulting in high levels of serum IgM and low levels of serum IgG, is caused by a defect in CD40L expression. The specific immune event that would be prevented by a defective CD40L would be", "opta": "activation of B cells by T-independent antigens", "optb": "failure of B cells to provide co-stimulation for Th2 activation", "optc": "failure of Th2 cells to provide co-stimulation for B cell isotype switching", "optd": "failure of Th2 cells to provide co-stimulation for B cell proliferation", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "DiGeorge's syndrome is characterized by the lack of a thymus The mouse model closest to this human disease would be a", "opta": "knock-out mouse for RAG-1 and RAG-2", "optb": "knock-out mouse for a thymus", "optc": "nude mouse", "optd": "recombinant mouse for CD3", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the Rous sarcoma virus has a homologous cellular protein?", "opta": "c-src", "optb": "v-src", "optc": "v-ha-src", "optd": "v-ha-ras", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Infants are most susceptible to bacterial infection due to low circulating levels of IgG", "opta": "in utero (before birth)", "optb": "at 0-3 months of age", "optc": "at 3-12 months of age", "optd": "at 12-24 months of age", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The chemical, typically released by the body in an allergic response is", "opta": "histamine", "optb": "allergens", "optc": "antihistamines", "optd": "perforins", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}